[
  {
    "problem": "5 - 2 = ",
    "answer": "3"
  },
  {
    "problem": "There are 9 birds sitting on a tree branch. 3 of them fly away. How many birds are left on the branch?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "problem": "5 + 1 = ",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Maria has 7 pencils, and she gives 3 of them to her sister. How many pencils does Maria have left?",
    "answer": "4"
  },
  {
    "problem": "10 - 3 = ",
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "problem": "Lucy has 8 marbles. She loses 2 marbles while playing. How many marbles does Lucy have now?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "problem": "12 - 6 = ",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "problem": "In a basket, there are 15 colorful balloons. If 9 balloons pop, how many balloons are still in the basket?",
    "answer": "6"
  },
  {
    "problem": "15 - 2 = ",
    "answer": "13"
  },
  {
    "problem": "If there are 6 cookies on a plate and Sarah eats 3 of them, how many cookies are left on the plate?",
    "answer": "3"
  }
]
